<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>ngyu.me</title><link href="http://ngyu.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://ngyu.github.io/feeds/review.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://ngyu.github.io/</id><updated>2013-12-03T10:20:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Using Pelican Themes</title><link href="http://ngyu.github.io/posts/2013/12/03/using-pelican-themes/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-12-03T10:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>ngyu</name></author><id>tag:ngyu.github.io,2013-12-03:posts/2013/12/03/using-pelican-themes/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Using Pelican Themes (https://github.com/getpelican/pelican-themes)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These instructions assume you have already read all the Pelican documentation, have a working site, and would now like to apply a non-default theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, choose a location to hold your themes. For this example, we'll use the directory ~/pelican-themes, but yours could be different. Clone the pelican-themes repository to that location on your local machine:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;git clone --recursive https://github.com/getpelican/pelican-themes ~/pelican-themes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you should have your pelican-themes repository stored at ~/pelican-themes/.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To use one of the themes, edit your Pelican settings file to include this line:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THEME = "/home/user/pelican-themes/theme-name"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, for instance, to use the mnmlist theme, you would edit your settings file to include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THEME = "/home/user/pelican-themes/mnmlist"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Save the changes to your settings file and then regenerate your site by using the Makefile you should already have set up using pelican-quickstart:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;make html&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Themes can also be specified directly via the -t ~/pelican-themes/theme-name parameter to the pelican command. If you want to edit your theme, make sure that any edits you make are made to the copy stored in ~/pelican-themes/theme-name. Any changes made to files stored in your site's output directory will be deleted the next time you generate your site.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="Pelican"></category></entry><entry><title>My First Review</title><link href="http://ngyu.github.io/posts/2010/12/03/my-first-review/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2010-12-03T10:20:00+01:00</updated><author><name>ngyu</name></author><id>tag:ngyu.github.io,2010-12-03:posts/2010/12/03/my-first-review/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Following is a review of my favorite mechanical keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="test"></category></entry></feed>